

#### **ABOUT ME**

Working with some of the most important internet companies across different areas. Got full stack experience creating and managing both websites and apps from the concept stage all the way to publishing. Love learning new things and tools every day. If I do not know something I will learn it.

## LINKS

## Personal Site:

https://panteliskassotis.com

#### LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/bearofleipzig

## GitHub:

https://github.com/pkassotis

## **Stack Overflow:**

https://stackoverflow.com/users/story/8929467

## **SKILL**

PROGRAMING LANGUAGES:
HTML5, CSS, C++, C#,
JAVASCRIPT, PYTHON3, PHP,
RUBY OTHER SKILLS: WEB
HOSTING, DNS HOSTING, APP
PUBLISHING, FINTECH, FLASH
ANIMATION MACHINE LEARNING,
UX EXPERIENCE,
INTERPERSONAL SKILLS,
STRATEGIC THINKING,
ANALYTICAL SKILLS,
PRIORITIZING

# PANTELIS KASSOTIS

Eleftheriou Venizelou 14B, Athens, 14565, Greece



(+30) 698 5033 632



info@panteliskassotis.com

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### **BLENDER**

Full-Time, Remote Jan 2020 - Present

## Product Development Engineer

Blender supports the entirety of the 3D pipeline—modeling, rigging, animation, simulation, rendering, compositing and motion tracking, even video editing and game creation. I mostly fix bugs, review code and create addons using Python, and C++.

#### **HACKERONE**

Contract, Remote Mar 2020 - Present

## Cyber Security Consultant

HackerOne was started by security leaders who are driven by a passion to make the internet safer. We partner with the global hacker community to surface the most relevant security issues of our customers before they can be exploited by criminals.

#### **HUNT CLUB**

Contract, Remote Dec 2020 - Present

### Information Technology Recruiter

Thanks to my role at GitHub and the Open Source community in general I come in contact with talented programmers every day so it makes sense to connect them with tech companies if they happen to be open to new opportunities.

## **EDUCATION**

## COMPUTER SCIENCE

New York, NY 2021

## MicroBachelors (MB), Computer Science Fundamentals

New York University I Tandon School of Engineering

## SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

Cambridge, MA 2020

## Advanced Professional Certifications (APCs), Web Programming, Mobile Apps, Game Development and Artificial Intelligence

<u>Harvard University I John A. Paulson School of Engineering and Applied Sciences</u>

### HOBBIES

SOCCER, KAYAKING, MUSIC PUBLISHING, WRITING